Hi everyone, in this video, we will introduce the Ai-Metal Generator for you.
You can enter keywords or get continuous materials from all sides.
You can check the generated text in the 3D window to see the effect on the clothing.
Choose a fabric type and run the Ai-Metal Generator.
In the fabric attribute bar, click the Ai-Metal Generator button next to default.
At the top of the dialogue window, you can set various options and enter keywords to generate text that fits all conditions as much as possible.
Below the keyword prompt, you can see the generated picture.
In the history record window, you can see the previously generated text.
The history record will be saved before you close the Marvelous Designer software.
At the top of each picture, you will see the various settings and keywords used to generate the AI picture.
Next, let's take a look at the various settings of the Ai-Metal Generator.
In the plant type, you can set the kind of seed.
The picture will be created based on the plant type you choose.
You must choose a plant type to generate the picture.
The pattern type is used to set the pattern type.
When choosing a type, you can select the pattern type at the bottom.
You can also choose the pattern type at the bottom.
The pictures created by the keyword will satisfy the pattern type and plant type you set.
Set the pattern type as a hard flower to generate multiple shapes.
If you only want to generate text based on the fabric type and the prompt, and do not want to set the pattern type, you can set the pattern type to .
You can set the AI Generator to generate the pictures in a regular order.
You can set the size of the picture and adjust the size of the picture.
When modifying the size of the pattern, the size of the bottom layer of the plant texture of the plant type will be retained.
If the size of the pattern is 1, then it will randomly generate a pattern with a width close to 1024 pixels.
If you set the size of the pattern to 4, then the width of the pattern will be close to 4096 pixels.
Therefore, when the size of the pattern is set to 1, it will generate a smaller duplicate pattern.
When the size of the pattern is set to 4, it will generate a larger duplicate pattern.
For this reason, I decided to use a Halloweenbottom of 55!
I thought about something else.
I was unable to show these things.
Let's see how they can be created вот
I can see the liberating pattern acquired by opening the next location somehow.
Let's look at another example.
When entering keywords, reading English will help you generate the picture you want more accurately.
When entering keywords, it is recommended that you describe through keywords rather than through long sentences.
Long sentences may lead to incorrect results, so it is recommended that you define keywords by dividing them into words and numbers.
When you have entered the keywords, click the Create button to generate the corresponding picture.
When the picture is generated, click the Apply button at the bottom to apply the texture.
If you want to emphasize a keyword, please emphasize it by using a keyword.
The keywords in the keyword will give more weight.
When you use one keyword, its weight will be 1.1 times, and when you use two keywords, it will be 1.2 times.
As the weight of the word green increases, we will see that the green area in the texture will increase more.
It can be seen that different weight will have different results.
When you click on History Record, the green area will change文字啊, the
blue area.
When the word automatic plus will give different colors, you can select various colors.
This is the change information, COVID-19 and the impact of COVID-19 on our country.
You can apply the previously generated picture to the fabric.
When you want to create a random picture, click on the random icon in the investment form, which will randomly apply pattern settings and set keywords.
The random function will only work for key word settings and pattern types. The tree type and pattern size you set will remain the original setting.
By random setting, you can create various types of pictures to enrich your creation.
The AI power generator will generate different results each time. Even if you input the same keywords, it will generate as many rich and colorful pictures as possible.
When you want to create a new picture that is similar to the previous result, or want to update some keywords, please click on the Keep Keywords button.
Click upon Production, you will see your released picturelooks is similar to the previous one.
You can view the previous history records, and from them, create new pictures.
Quick menu with articles is possible with most of the data.
If you modify the keywords, the results might be based on additions and corrections of keywords amounted to your previous post.
It may take a certain amount of time to create a picture, so you can click the arrow button in the upper right corner to fold the window.
When waiting for the picture to be created, you can continue to adjust the costume or other changes.
When the picture is created, the folded window will remind you that the picture has been created.
Open the window and click the arrow button in the upper right corner again.
This is the introduction of the AI Principle Creator. You can add more interesting content to your design through this function.
Thank you for watching. See you in the next video.